AMIRA GUCHER - BLACKMAN

Full-Stack Web Developer

Personal Profile

Prior to studying at the School of Code my studies evolved around Art and Design, and then Psychology. During the bootcamp I found a true passion for coding which has only grown over time. I have experience of working with people from all walks of life and have gained the ability to work within a team and in an agile framework. Through the School of Code, I have developed both leadership and team work skills and the ability to problem solve and come up with solutions. I am committed, hardworking, pro-active and passionate and am ready to contribute to a company's successes.

Recent Experience

Recently graduated from the School Of Code bootcamp. During the bootcamp I was introduced to a wide range of programming utilities and languages which has given me the confidence and understanding of a wide variety of areas within tech. I have gained the ability to work within an agile framework and have experience working within a tight time schedule and under pressure.

- Training in agile development
- Weekly Hackathons and presentations
- Trained in a range of technologies (as shown in skills section)
- Experience with leadership and project management
- Experience with working within a team successfully
- · Advanced design skills with Figma and Miro



Work Experience

Personal Carer: Septermber 2018 - June 2021

• Cared for an individual on a weekly basis

Old Town Trader: June 2020 - August 2020

• Warehouse Assistant

Artist Anon: May 2019 - January 2020

Sales Assistant

Robert Dyas August 2017 - March 2019

Sales Assistant

ICS: Junuary 2018 - March 2018

Volunteer

Contact

Number: 07913686584

Email: amiragucher@gmail.com

Location: Nottingham

GitHub

www.github.com/amiragucher

LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/amira-gucherblackman-

Education

School Of Code Bootcamper | 2022

16 week bootcamp

University Of Brighton | 2019-21

Psychology and Counselling BS

Brighton Metropolitan College | 2018-19

Psychology Access to Higher Education course

Sussex Downs College | 2015-17

Art and Design Btech

Moira House School | 2008-15

GCSE's including English and Maths.

Languages

- Auth0
- Next js
- CSS
- Node
- Cypress
- Postgress
- Express
- Postman
- Figma
- React
- Heroku
- Tailwind
- HTML
- Typescript
- Javascript
- Typescrip
- Jest
- Vercel
- Miro